Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Alumni Association Records, 1895-2012 UA.6.5.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
University of Pittsburgh Alumni Association Records
1895-2012
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Pitt Alumni Association
UA.6.5.1
56.25 Linear Feet
The University of Pittsburgh Alumni Association's mission is to advance the University and enrich students and alumni worldwide. Begun as a social organization, the association now offers programs for alumni and encourages them to contribute their time, talent, and resources for the benefit of the University and other alumni. This collection documents these activities as well as the day-to-day operations of the Association.
Previous Citation
University of Pittsburgh Alumni Association Records, 1895-2012, UA.6.5.1, University Archives, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Arrangement
The collection consists of eleven series:
Series I. Administrative Files, 1980-2007
Series II. Alumni Council and Board of Trustees, 1869-2007
Series III. Finances, 1992-2006
Series IV. Constituent Groups, 1991-2006
Series V. Alumni Networking, 1986-2001
Series VI. Events, 1986-2007
Series VII. Programs and Projects, 1994-2007
Series VIII. Professional Organizations, 1999-2006
Series IX. Publications, 1925-2012
Series X. Early History, 1895-1952
Series XI. Assorted Records, 1983-2010
Series XII. Audio-Visual Materials, 1988-2011
Access Restrictions
Material in the following boxes are restricted: Scholarships Box 6, Nominations Committee Box 17 Folder 13 through Box 19 Folder 18.
Scope and Content Notes
The Alumni Association of the University of Pittsburgh Records document the activities of the Association as it works to serve the University and provide social events for alumni. Much of the material concerns the Association's day-to-day operations through the documentation of normal business activities, such as memoranda, correspondence, meeting minutes, agenda and packets for meetings, presentations, talking points, conference materials, election and nomination materials, and materials related to the Council of Alumni Association Executives and the Council for Advancement and Support of Education (CASE). The earliest records include meeting minutes (1908-1914), an undated grade report, alumni yearbooks, commencement programs, and a piece of correspondence regarding the Alumni Banquet of 1899. The most recent records consist of copies of the Association newsletter, the "Alumni Connection", from 2012.
Together these records consist of meeting minutes, by-laws, constitutions, magazines, newsletters, memoranda, correspondence including to and from the Chancellor, presentations, talking points, architectural drawings and design plans of the Alumni offices in Alumni Hall, strategic plans, quarterly planning documents, fundraising documents, event planning documents, conference materials, surveys, mailings sent to members and membership mailing lists, goals and objectives, board meeting packets, personnel files, resumes, advocacy records, sheet music, cartoons, and published journals of CASE.
The collection is rich in information pertaining to the policy decisions of the Association throughout its history, its relationships with its constituency groups and the University.
History
The Alumni Association of the Western University of Pennsylvania was formed on June 27, 1866, when a group of alumni agreed to meet for dinner once a year. The earliest known constitution and by-laws were accepted on June 29, 1892. The organization adopted the name General Alumni Association in February 1897. A new constitution and by-laws were adopted when the Western University of Pennsylvania became the University of Pittsburgh in 1908. The constitution and by-laws were once again adapted when the organization changed its name to the University of Pittsburgh Alumni Association on April 6, 1988.
The University of Pittsburgh Alumni Association's mission is to offer programs for alumni and encourage them to contribute their time, talent, and resources for the benefit of the University and other alumni, and to serve as advocates for the University within the Pittsburgh community, in the commonwealth of Pennsylvania, and throughout the world. The Alumni Association of the University of Pittsburgh Records document the activities of the Association as it works to serve the University and provide social and educational events for alumni. Much of the material concerns the association's day-to-day operations through the documentation of normal business activities, such as memoranda, correspondence, meeting minutes, agenda and packets for meetings, presentations, talking points, conference materials, election and nomination materials, and materials related to the Council of Alumni Association Executives and the Council for Advancement and Support of Education.
The earliest records include meeting minutes (1908-1914), an undated grade report, alumni yearbooks, commencement programs, and a piece of correspondence regarding the Alumni Banquet of 1899. The collection is rich in information pertaining to the policy decisions of the association throughout its history, its relationships with its constituency groups and the University.
Slides (Photographs); CD-ROMs; Video recordings; Videocassettes; University of Pittsburgh alumni review; Alumni news review (University of Pittsburgh General Alumni Association); Pitt Advocate; Alumni connections (Pitt Alumni Association); Universities and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; University of Pittsburgh; Minutes; Financial records; Administrative records; National Society of Fund Raising Executives; University of Pittsburgh. Alumni Legislative Network; Patouillet, Leland; Council of Alumni Association Executives; Council for Advancement and Support of Education; Nordenberg, Mark A.; University of Pittsburgh -- Alumni and alumnae; Western University of Pennsylvania. Alumni Association; University of Pittsburgh. Alumni Association; University of Pittsburgh. General Alumni Association; Pitt Alumni Association; Pitt Alumni Recruitment Team; University of Pittsburgh. Alumnae Council; University of Pittsburgh. Alumni Council; National Collegiate Athletic Association; University of Pittsburgh. African American Alumni Council
- Administrative Files, 1980-2007; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  The records in this series detail the general operations of the office and staff of the Alumni Association as they perform their duties to lead the organization. It includes items regarding personnel (including former Executive Director Leland Patouillet) and membership, board meetings and meetings with individuals, strategic planning, scholarships, and the Alumni Legislative Network.
  - Information Files, 1.
    - Leland Patouillet
      - Biographical Profile (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Travel, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Vacation Requests, 1998-2006 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Travel Advance Requests, 2001-2007 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Business Travel Requests, 2001-2007 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Travel and Business Files, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
      - Disbursement Requests, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - NC State Trip, February 19-21, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - MBNA Conference, April 25-27, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Alumni Association Fundraising Campaign, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Alumni Association Fundraising Campaign Correspondence, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Speech, Blue and Gold Society, 1997, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Speeches, General, 1989-2004 (Box 1, Folder 14-16)
      - Sample Presentations, 2001-2005 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Alumni Awards Dinner Presentation, June 22, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Board of Trustees Presentation, February 19, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Alumni Association Report Presentation, February 20, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - CCFA Presentation, October 8, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Institutional Advancement Presentations, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Presentation with Al Novak (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Reading, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Dissertation, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Dissertation Research, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Dissertation Presentation, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - CASE, 1991-1999 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - CASE Publication, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Fall Consulting, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 30-31)
      - University of South Florida Alumni Association Manual, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Dorothea de Zafra Atwell (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - John R. Bender (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Arthur Bloom (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Bibiano Boerio (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Daniel Boyd (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Robert Bragdon (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Becky Brandt (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Dean Carey (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Joseph E. Castagnino (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Jeffrey Cooper (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Christine Dockey (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Dolores Ellenberg (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - David Farrell (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Ilene Fingeret (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Syndey Forbes (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Grace Fratangelo (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Pamela Golden (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Heather Harmon (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Trish Rall Henniger (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Frances Hesselbein (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Steve Hudson (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Marvin Perry Jones (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Marcia Klingensmith (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Chuck Knoll (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Andrew Kuzneski, Sr. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Ignatius Laux (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Beth Hoffman Leon (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Portia McGonigal (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Caitlin McLaughlin (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Joseph Macerelli (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Charles Jay Miller (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Felix Miller (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Joseph Mills (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Chancellor Mark Nordenberg (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Chancellor J. Dennis O'Connor (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - William Pope (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Brent Saunders (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Matthew Singerman (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - James Smith (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - James Thompson (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Dana Warren (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - John Woodruff (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Brad Wyland (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Membership, 2.
    - Alumni Association Membership, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Demographics, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Student Recruitment, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Life Membership, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Dues Implementation, 1980-1992 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Membership Dues, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Alumni Dues and Annual Fund Survey, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Prospective Alumni Donors, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Member Emails, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Member Email Updates/Service Requests, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Mailing Lists, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - International Alumni, 1995-2001 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - International Alumni Outreach, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 2-6)
  - Miscellaneous Meetings, 3.
    - Meetings with Athletics, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Meetings with Eva Bloom, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Meetings with Maureen Cross Bolden, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Meetings with Terry Brown, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Meetings with Career Services, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Meetings with Pat Carver, 2000, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Meeting with G. Reynolds Clark, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Meetings with Jack Daniel, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Meeting with Dave Dalessandro, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Meetings with Sandi Demas, 2005, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Meeting with Herb Douglas, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Meeting with Jean Ferketish, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Meetings with Brian Generalovich, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Meetings with Martin Grenzebach, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Meetings with Robert Hill, 2000, 2001, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Meetings with Kathy Humphrey, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Meetings with Mary Jean Lovett, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Meeting with Jim McCarl, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Meeting with Jim Maher, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Meeting with Cindi Moore, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Meetings with Carmelle Nickens, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Meetings with Chancellor Mark Nordenberg, 2005-2007 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Meetings with Al Novak, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 29-30)
    - Meeting with Sheila Rathke, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Meeting with Cindy Roth, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Meetings with Marvin Roth, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Meetings with Keith Schaefer, 2004-2006 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Meetings with Senior Staff, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Meetings with Julie Shepard, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Meetings with Alyson Wallach, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Board Meetings, 4.
    - Winter Board Meeting & Scholars Reception, February 6, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Fall Board Meeting, October 27, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Fall Board Meeting, October 24, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Winter Board Meeting, February 28, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Winter Board Meeting Correspondence, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Fall Board Meeting, October 22, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Fall Board Meeting Correspondence, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Fall Board Meeting RSVPs, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Winter Board Meeting, February 26, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Winter Board Meeting Correspondence, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Annual Board Meeting, May 21, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Annual Board Meeting, June 10, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Annual Board Meeting, May 19, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Annual Board Meeting Correspondence, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Annual Board Meeting, May 17, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Annual Board Meeting Correspondence, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Annual Board Meeting, April 23, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Annual Board Meeting Correspondence, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Annual Board Meeting, April 30, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Annual Board Meeting Correspondence, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Strategic Planning, 5.
    - Strategic Planning Process (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Prelude to Strategic Planning (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Long Range Strategic Plan, December, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Long Range Strategic Plan, 1992-1997 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Five Year Strategic Plan, June, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Long Range Strategic Plan, 1998-2002 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Strategic Plan Slideshow, 1998-2002 (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
    - Long Range Strategic Plan, 2003-2005 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Strategic Plan, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Strategic Plan, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Strategic Plan, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 7-8)
    - Strategic Plan, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Strategic Planning Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Strategic Planning Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 11-12)
    - Strategic Planning Committee, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Strategic Planning Committee, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Strategic Planning Committee, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Alumni Association Ad Hoc Campaign Strategy Committee Report, March 6, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Alumni Legislative Network Strategic Plan, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Alumni Legislative Network Strategic Plan, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 18-19)
    - CAAE Strategic Planning Committee, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Strategic Planning Consultants Report, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Strategic Planning Consultants Meeting, October 10-12, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 22-23)
    - Strategic Planning Consultants Report, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Scholarships (Restricted), 6.
    - Scholarship Proposal, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Bowling Green State University Legacy Scholarship Information, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Scholarship Account Information, 1992-2004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Freshmen Scholarships, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Pitt Club Scholarships, 1993-2004 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Scholarship Brochure, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - General Scholarships, 1995-2004 (Box 6, Folder 7-9)
    - Scholarship Budget Reports, 1997-2003 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Pitt Alumni Scholarship Program Criteria Response Forms, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Tom Ablauf Memorial Scholarship, 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 12-13)
    - Scholarship and Student Recruitment Committee, 1998-2003 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Endowed Scholarships, 1998-2005 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Scholarship Recipients, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 16-17)
    - Scholarship Thank-You Letters, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Legislative Network, 7.
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast Correspondence, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - ALN Breakfast- Philadelphia, March 12, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - ALN Breakfast- Philadelphia Correspondence, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - ALN Breakfast- Pittsburgh, May 30, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - ALN Breakfast- Pittsburgh Attendees, May 30, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Correspondence, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Attendees, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Pictures, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Correspondence, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Attendees, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Publications, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Pictures, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Correspondence, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Attendees, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Correspondence, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Attendees, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Publicity, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Correspondence, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Attendees, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Publicity, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Correspondence, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Attendees, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Correspondence, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast- Attendees, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - ALN Legislative Breakfast, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Pitt Day in Harrisburg, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Pitt Day in Harrisburg, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Pitt Day in Harrisburg, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Legislative Network, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Alumni Legislative Network, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Legislative Network, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Alumni Legislative Network, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Alumni Legislative Network, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - ALN Alumni Association Board Meeting Reports, 2000-2004 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - ALN Membership Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - ALN Committee Meetings, 1999-2005 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - ALN Recruitment Packet, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - ALN Recruitment Letter, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - ALN Recruitment Letter, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - ALN Action Alerts, 1994-2005 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - ALN Planning, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - ALN Planning- Correspondence, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - ALN Planning, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - ALN Member Handbook, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - ALN Membership (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - ALN Members, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - ALN Members- North Hills, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - ALN Receptions, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - ALN Reception for Public Officials, May 4, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - ALN Orientation, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - ALN Orientation, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - ALN Budget Presentation, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - ALN Budget, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - ALN Goals & Strategies, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - ALN Publicity, 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Letters to the Editor RE: Post Gazette Article, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ALN Brochures, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Pitt Magazine Ad, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Pitt Magazine Ad, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Pitt Magazine Ad, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - ALN Legislative Proposal, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - ALN Survey of Alumni Legislative Networks, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - ALN Department Transfer, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Bigelow Boulevard Public Hearing, July 23, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Bigelow Boulevard Public Hearing- Correspondence, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Bigelow Boulevard Task Force, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Bigelow Boulevard Task Force- Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Bigelow Boulevard Publicity & Responses, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Institute of Politics, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Environmental Law Clinic, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - License Plate Initiative, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Funding Award, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - ALN Student Program, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Grassroots Planning Information, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 20-21)
    - Grassroots Solutions Correspondence, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Lobbying Information, 1998-2002 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - ALN Quarterly Lobbying Reports, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - ALN Philadelphia Trip, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Philadelphia Area Alumni, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Philadelphia Area Alumni, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Philadelphia Area Alumni, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Pennsylvania Alumni Prospects, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - CURRENTS Correspondence, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - CommonGOAL (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Timothy Pecsenye Correspondence, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Faxes to Chancellor's Office, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Branch Campus Legislative Work, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Cathedral Prints for Congressmen, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence RE: Federal Officials, 1998-2004 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Alumni Groups at Other Universities (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Legislator Information, 2000-2003 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Alumni Council and Board of Trustees, 1869-2007; II.
  The records in this series relate to the governing documents of the Alumni Association and the decisions made by the Alumni Council and the Board of Trustees. It contains governing documents, records of Alumni Council, meeting minutes from the Board of Directors and Board of Trustees, minutes from the Executive Board, board retreat information, and records of the Nominations Committee and the Institutional Advancement Committee.
  - Governing Documents, 1.
    - Mission Statement (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Current Constitution and Bylaws (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Original Constitution, June 22, 1869 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Constitution and Bylaws, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Bylaws, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Council & General Meetings, 2.
    - General Alumni Association Minutes, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - General Alumni Association Minutes, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - General Alumni Association Minutes, 1910 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - General Alumni Association Minutes, 1911 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - General Alumni Association Minutes, 1912 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - General Alumni Association Minutes, 1913 (Box 10, Folder 11)